This has
Speaker 1: probably happened to you every couple months or so. You
look up
Speaker 1: from what you're doing, otherwise occupied, feeding the dog or paying your power bill, and you look up, and they'll be trying once again to make Roseanne Barr be quiet. Shut up, Roseanne Barr! You're a Nazi! You're crazy! It's
not
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): working! Roseanne Barr's been in the public eye for almost 40 years, and amazingly...
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): She's more influential than ever. So we thought we would check in with her and see how she's doing. Roseanne Barr, how are you? I'm great, Tucker. How are you? You're obviously unbowed. I can't remember where I was the other day, and someone was like, Roseanne Barr's a Nazi. She's an anti-Semite. I'm thinking, you can probably criticize her. Probably not a Nazi or an anti-Semite.
Speaker 3: Probably not.
So
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): what?
Speaker 3: they canceled,
Speaker 4: famously, they canceled the resurgence of your show, the relaunch of your
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): show. Just like you, when it was number one, hey, how come they, why did they, don't their shareholders wonder why they would do that? I don't know
Speaker 6: how that spooky finance stuff works. I
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): don't either.
I've still got
Speaker 6: some questions, I will say that.
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): But did you figure out, like I did, that it's really personal?
Speaker 7: Oh, it's always personal. The thing about television is everything's personal on TV. Yeah, it's about you. Yeah. So that's great when everyone's
Speaker 8: like, oh, you're Jesus. But it's not so good when
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): they're like, you're fired. I don't take any of it personally, thank you,
Speaker 9: Kevin. But you get fired in this very, very public way, become the center of the national debate over Trump. But you don't go away. And then all of a sudden, I look up and you're everywhere. How did
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): that happen?
- I don't
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): know how it happened. I
really
Speaker 11: don't.
Speaker 12: - Did you expect to be doing this at this stage of your life?
Speaker 11: - No, I, no. Well, I guess when I was really little, I saw myself doing something that was gonna be, have good consequences
to it.
Speaker 11: And so anyways, this week I was like, hey,
This
Speaker 11: is like when you were little, and now you're doing it. It was one of
Speaker 13: those minutes where you
Speaker 14: go, thank you, God, because I do feel like God puts me where he wants me. I
Speaker 15 (higher-pitched voice): mean, I'll tell
Speaker 16: you all that later, but
I
Speaker 15 (higher-pitched voice): go like, hey, I'm a lady citizen journalist for my old age. Hell,
Speaker 11: that's great. It's great because, you know, I love
Speaker 13: that. Oh, no, I can't remember her name, but that one that used to interview everybody in the 50s.
She
Speaker 13: had her own show and she did the greatest interviews. I'm so stupid, I can't remember her name.
Speaker 17: Jake, check that lady out, my son. -
Lady
Speaker 18: in the 50s who used to interview people.
Speaker 17: - She had a great
Speaker 11: interview show. Anyway, but I like being a citizen journalist. Like, you know, like you're a real journalist, you know?
Speaker 13: But you're also a writer, which astounds me because we never see that anywhere. I mean, you are such a great writer. So I want to talk to you about that, and I look forward to doing
Speaker 19: that. But you are such a great writer because I
have so much to
Speaker 13: say. I want to say it like this. Let me think.
I'm a
Speaker 13: deeply religious Jew, which is why they call me a Nazi. Of course. So I'm like...
- And a
Speaker 13: racist.
Speaker 20: -
Speaker 11: Yeah, of course. -
And a
Speaker 11: transphobe and whatever. A Zionist baby killer, they call me everything. And before that, when I was on the left, the right used to, but they're the same, I guess. It's all the same people. They're playing different
Speaker 13: parts. They used to call me a cow, a whole, you know, destroying the American dream, man-hater. You know, they're always throwing
Speaker 11: stuff at me and none of it was ever true.
But I
Speaker 11: had to live through all that gauntlet of hate since I first showed up. Sorry,
Speaker 21: we haven't answered your question. It's Arlene Francis.
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): No! Not Arlene. She was good, though. Barbara Walters. Not Barbara Walters. I knew her. She was good, though, with Anwar Sadat. Wasn't she? No. No. She was kind of an ugly little woman with brown
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): hair.
Speaker 22: Okay. So an ugly
Speaker 23: little woman with brown
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): hair. Vaye Emerson?
Speaker 23: No. Wendy Berry?
No.
Speaker 23: Check, Google ugly little woman with brown hair, 1950s.
Speaker 15 (higher-pitched voice): The greatest interview, Mae Brussels.
Thank
Speaker 24: you, God.
Speaker 25: Mae Brussels. Was this on Salt Lake City stations?
Speaker 24: Yeah,
Speaker 13: my dad used to watch it. Okay. And he'd say, this woman has integrity. You know, my dad used to decode media for me. Yes. Because he wanted to be a comedian. So he always showed me how comedy
Speaker 11: works in, you know, anyway.
Oh my
Speaker 11: god, I can't even focus my mind. But anyway. So you said you're
a
Speaker 27: deeply religious Jew.
Speaker 11: Yeah, and since I
Speaker 13: was three years old, I wrote it in my third book called Rose Anarchy. I've
had a conversation going
Speaker 13: with God. I wrote it in my book. You know how little kids have an imaginary friend? Yes. Well, mine was God. It's kind of weird. You chose wisely. Yeah, because that's all we studied. It was an Orthodox Jewish family.
Speaker 13: And so that was my friend, and I talked to him when I would read and study. I wanted to know everything about it, you know, and I would talk to him. And he'd always answer this in my book. I said, how come you could solve every problem on Earth? All you've got to do is just
Speaker 29: wiggle your little finger, and you can stop all these problems. Why can't you do that? All you have to do is wiggle your finger. Because I was a suffering child.
Speaker 13: Yes.
And he
Speaker 13: said to me, "Because I don't have fingers, Roseanne, but you do." And he said, "And you should be very proud of that opposable thumb that I put on that hand of yours because now you can really get busy helping a lot of people and trying to make things right." And he always gave me the answer that I knew God would give me. He didn't ever go, "Yeah, go get them."
Speaker 13: "Yeah, they're wrong in their religion." He didn't never say none of that. So I knew it was him, you know. So he told me all the time, "Go over here and do this, and go over there and do that. "And just trust me on this." And I did that my whole life, with the exception of a few marriages that really effed me up.
Speaker 30: But then
I
Speaker 13: got rid of those guys and continued on the path I was supposed to go on.
-
Speaker 31: Did you not ask for guidance on the marriages?
You know, I didn't
Speaker 11: listen. Yeah. It wasn't God's fault. Yeah, he told me, but I go, I'm putting you on hold.
Speaker 13: Yeah. I got some physical business that you don't want to know
Speaker 11: about.
Do you think he knew? Well,
Speaker 11: yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But it wasn't anything. I was married, so it wasn't anything...
Speaker 11: bad. Right. I mean, except for that it was horrible sex. Which, you know, people should not have sex. That's one way that we can fix the world right now.
Is people
Speaker 33: stop having sex? Yes, absolutely. That's a tough one. It's harder than quitting smoking or something. I
Speaker 11: know. Unless you're married and you can take care of the kids that are going to be a result of it. Yes. Right? Isn't that common sense?
Speaker 34: I strongly
Speaker 11: agree. And we have...
Speaker 11: journalists such as yourself with
Speaker 13: a conscience who care about this country and
Speaker 29: what it means and
how we have
Speaker 29: to do everything we can to save it at this late late date for all of us hello yes and stop buying in the bullshit you know I said that it to introduce
Speaker 29: the potus the deep state bullshit
Speaker 1: actually it's funny you mention that we have that clip
really
Speaker 29: yes
Speaker 1: oh roseanne bar this is your life here you are
Speaker 37: aren't we all fed up with the deep state we
say bullshit we say bullshit we say bullshit we say bullshit we say bullshit we say bullshit and that
Speaker 37: bullshit
Speaker 37: We want Trump, the Magador,
Speaker 39: to kill that goddamn bull! And the bullshit, kill that goddamn bull!
Speaker 1: Okay. Now,
I just put the
Speaker 1: political analysis on hold for two seconds. You're obviously enjoying that immensely.
Speaker 40: Oh, I'm sorry.
Speaker 40: It was so fun.
It
Speaker 11: was so awesome to, you know, it's always fun to make people laugh and, you know, come alive.
So, I think even if
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): like you didn't like Trump and you weren't going to vote for Trump, you'd look at that and be like, that
looks like a pretty good time. Oh,
Speaker 41: no, I wouldn't do it if I- Well,
Speaker 42: of course. I don't mean you. But like, how could anyone watch that? I wouldn't
be out
Speaker 42: there doing that for nobody. You're wearing a cowboy hat. Yeah. Screaming obscenities. You
Speaker 41: did? And they didn't have the mic. So I had to stand on my tiptoes, which, you know, I could
Speaker 11: barely reach the mic.
Speaker 11: But, yeah, I swiped this hat off a guy and, you know, I don't like how my hair looked.
Speaker 41: Don't you like how my hair, you know, I cut my own hair with toenail clippers. It took me four days, but I cut it hair by hair
Speaker 43: because I was so sick of it. But, yeah, I had it. Yeah, of course
Speaker 44: in the mirror. I'm not crazy. Did anyone see you do it?
Speaker 29: Good.
I was
Speaker 29: in a room by myself, but
Speaker 11: no, but I loved it and I had spent a lovely week down there at Mar-a-Lago. It was so awesome and I just loved it.
Speaker 9: What do you think of Trump the guy? You know him, obviously. What do you think of him?
Well, as I
Speaker 11: always say, he's the only guy in my
Speaker 13: Hollywood career that ever returned a favor. He's the only one who ever returned a favor and gave me back more than I had ever.
Speaker 13: given him i think he has such integrity
Speaker 11: i think he's like me a lot he he says he tries to be funny and he is really funny yeah the guy's really funny he's got great timing and i i i laugh so you know we all laugh i mean we all think he's funny what what
Speaker 46: favorite did he return
Speaker 47: well you know i did i i was doing my i think it was my second or third hbo
Hey,
Speaker 48: it's Tucker Carlson. The internet is crowded with interesting things that don't really matter. On TCN, we attempt to bring you interesting things that actually do matter, and a lot of them. Interviews, long form and short, videos, documentaries.
You can
Speaker 49 (lower-pitched voice): find all of it on TuckerCarlson.com, and we hope you will.
We'll see you next time.